Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
Ms. Da-reum.
I'm not into men.
- What?
- Also...
there's this woman
I'm interested in right now.
What?
Director Lee.
How did you find us here?
I heard about the covert op.
Ms. Kim told me that you had trouble
trying to get Master Im on board.
I came out to help.
At this hour?
Did you really come for work?
Of course.
I'm that serious about work.
So, well...
There are only two rooms.
I can crash in his room.
- You, in my room?
- It's not like I can take her room.
Well, that wasn't what I meant.
It's nothing new between us.
Get away from me.
I won't misunderstand
the situation anymore, Mr. Kang.
Don't worry.
"Misunderstand"?
Well, if it's
too inconvenient for you
I can sleep out in the hall.
No, you should take one of the rooms.
- I'll share mine with him.
- Okay.
Okay. Then it's decided.
We'll take this one.
- Good night.
- Have a good rest.
You have a thing
for Director Lee Chan.
For a long time.
I mean, me?
- Jeez.
- Da-reum is unbelievable.
What about me gives off that vibe?
Are you disappointed
that she doesn't think of you
as a man?
Whatever.
Gosh.
I can tell
that you care about Da-reum.
Concerned? Hardly.
She's new to work.
That's why I'm looking out for her.
Looking out for someone and actually
caring for them aren't the same.
It's different.
Wait, Ms. Nam.
- What?
- Also...
there's this woman
I'm interested in right now.
What?
I could see today
that you two have grown close.
I had a feeling
that you might be interested in her.
I'm not.
Even if I did
it's impossible for a CEO
to date a rookie.
So Mr. Kang wasn't into men.
Who's the woman he's interested in?
Come on, Da-reum.
Why do you want to know that?
Come on.
Could it be someone at work?
Yes, just like that.
Don't let it get tangled.
Like that.
That's it. Carefully.
Okay. Good.
You have a knack for this.
Did you have trouble sleeping too?
Yes.
And I saw the light was on.
Come here and join me.
May I?
It's best to move your hands
when you're stressed out.
Knotting may seem like a job
where you tie things
but you'll come to learn
that it can untangle your heart.
You're right.
Tying knots helped me clear my head.
- You should give it a go too.
- Okay.
- Do what you did yesterday.
I let my feelings
get ahead of me yesterday.
I shouldn't have said it like that.
So even if Master Im
doesn't agree to be on board
I hope you two can make
these traditional knots more visible.
We completely understand
what you mean.
I'm happy to know that you do.
Please continue to practice.
I'll get breakfast ready.
- Sure.
- And this one.
I'm taking your first knot.
Ta-da. I made a new one.
I learned it just now.
- You've learned it already?
- Yes.
Do you want me to teach you?
Sure.
Let's do it.
All right. Take a good look.
Put the green cord
on top of the pink one
and create a knot.
Good. Now do you see this space here?
Spread it out a little.
Look, it's a heart.
Then hold the top
and make a wing on each side.
- A wing...
- Yes.
Then hold the top
and pull it to the side.
The young lady
who came from Seoul made this.
She tried rather hard
after just one day.
Isn't that admirable?
Master Im.
I apologize for yesterday.
I knew your intentions very well.
It's always tough
to be a teacher.
I must always keep an eye
on people's feelings as I proceed...
but at times,
I find myself blurting out words
that can turn into sharp blades.
Are you
apologizing right now?
I was just afraid.
That everything we have stood for
would disappear down that road.
It won't disappear, Master Im.
How beautiful.
These are so pretty.
When did you come out?
Just now.
They looked so pretty from the window
so I came out to see them up close.
I'm sorry for that day.
It had been weighing on my mind
after you left like that.
Please don't mind me.
You suffered from a misunderstanding
because of me.
It must've put you in a tough spot.
She and I had already broken up.
She must've said
all those mean things to you
out of spite for me.
I apologize.
I'm really fine.
I'm okay, really.
Da-reum.
There's something I want to show you.
Can you spare me some time
on our way back to Seoul?
A lot went through my mind
after learning how to make knots.
Traditional knots
are a form of art and meditation
not something
you can print with a machine.
I brought up words
like factory production
without realizing
how deep the practice was.
I apologize.
And because we desperately
wanted to work with you
I also had forgotten
about the core of my business.
Appello strives
to maintain value that will last
instead of fast-paced trends.
So what if we provided
an experience for the people
in the exact traditional way
of your practice?
How about putting together a DIY kit
so people can try making
traditional Korean knots
with all the materials
and instructions at home?
I thought
it was very difficult to make knots
but I had so much fun
when I got my hands on it.
I'm sure many people will love it.
Perhaps it's more meaningful
to have knots
created by many new hands
instead of ones made
by a single artisan.
If you're going to make it,
make it right.
The traditional knot kit.
Thank you, Master Im.
- Thank you, ma'am.
- However...
there is one condition.
I won't allow you to make something
with half-hearted instructions.
They must have hands-on experience
as they learn to make actual knots.
Do you mean that people must
take part in the experience?
That's what will actually last.
I'll see what you come up with
before I go ahead
and give you my final approval.
- Hop in, Ms. Nam.
- Okay.
Ms. Da-reum, let's go in my car.
You'd probably prefer to go alone.
Come with me. His car
isn't built for long-distance trips.
What do you mean?
I'd get there an hour before you.
Hey.
My seats come with a massager.
You can lie down flat on my seat.
Ms. Da-reum,
whose car do you want to take?
First of all,
can you let my hands go?
Then...
I'm sorry for that day.
There's something I want to show you.
Can you spare me some time
on our way back to Seoul?
May I take
Director Lee's car?
You'll also find
that more convenient.
All right, then.
Was my car uncomfortable?
No, it was such a comfortable ride.
I just felt bad
that you always had to give me rides.
I'll take Ms. Da-reum home.
Have a safe trip back.
Thank you.
Hey, Ha-gi.
Drive safely.
Sure.
Do you know where you are?
It's a bus stop in my neighborhood.
D.N.X FOREVER
LET'S STAY TOGETHER FOREVER
Oh, this...
You wrote this.
How did you know that?
Do you remember this photo book?
This is...
Chan.
EXCLUSIVE:
WHERE IS D.N.X'S LEE CHAN NOW?
DISAPPEARED AFTER THEY DISBANDED
D.N.X DISBANDS AFTER 3 YEARS
I can't believe D.N.X still has fans.
I thought they were over.
- Be quiet.
- I'm not wrong.
I feel bad for her.
It must be embarrassing.
D.N.X FOREVER
WE WILL BE TOGETHER FOREVER
"DESTINY NEVER X,"
I KNOW I'LL SEE YOU ON STAGE AGAIN
I can't believe you still had this.
When I was going through
the toughest time after we disbanded
this journal helped me stay strong.
I didn't expect you
to hold this so dearly.
During those toughest days,
I went and looked for these places.
I thought I'd perhaps see you.
D.N.X FOREVER
LET'S STAY TOGETHER FOREVER
The person who continued
to show me their support somewhere.
And now, we've finally met.
This is fascinating.
I also spent
a lot of time sitting here
listening to your songs
just trying to get through life.
We have
always been supporting each other
from a distance, right?
How about...
we stay by each other's side
from now on?
Sorry?
I want to start dating you.
Da-reum.
I want
to get to know you more.
I thought you were
hitting it off with the CEO.
What's this plot twist?
Did Chan really ask you out first?
Yes.
No way.
This is straight out of Notting Hill.
I can't believe Chan is
Namda's first potential boyfriend.
This is why you should
never give up on something.
So? What did you say to him?
I haven't said anything.
I'm still thinking about it.
You're thinking?
Why would you do that?
I also want to know
what he's really like
not as a celebrity,
but a real person.
But if I rushed into this,
I might ruin all my great memories.
I got a bit scared.
Try going on three dates.
It's not something
you can conclude by thinking.
You should
be loved as Nam Da-reum,
not just as a fan.
You deserve that much
after staying loyal for 12 years.
As Nam Da-reum?
You said you were interested
in another woman?
Jeez. You deserved this.
What? "Another woman"?
Another woman?
Hey, why not just say
you were interested in women?
Why did you say "another woman"?
That's why she took "another" car.
Well, it looks like
another girl has had her heart broken
and is giving up on love.
Hey, do you think that was
bad enough for her to move on?
Of course she would.
Why wouldn't she?
She'd make a checkmate move.
You're looking disappointed.
- You can be so cute, you know.
- Cut it out.
Hey. Just be honest.
"You're the woman I'm interested in."
Why can't you say it? Why?
Shut up.
You should go home.
You'll lose her and sit in regret.
- Hey, go. Get out of here!
- Come on.
I was about to leave anyway.
You and your temper.
That's why all the girls
who liked you ended up leaving.
Why, that...
Still, I'm jealous.
Hey, Luni.
- Yes?
- Put on some classical music.
I'll play classical music
perfect for the night.
I know very well
that we can never be.
That we can never be.
...we can never be.
We can never be...
No.
She wouldn't have moved on.
She wouldn't have
moved on that easily.
Oh, come on!
KOREA HERITAGE SERVICE
ANNOUNCEMENTS
Now, let us check.
Gosh. Please.
- Hurry up and click it.
- Okay. I will. Be quiet.
The fashion sector.
SELECTED: SE CORPORATION
MOSAIC BOJAGI
- It's SE.
- It's not us.
"The modern reinterpretation
of traditional bojagi
was highly regarded for its potential
to reach a wider audience."
Wait, one second. Over here.
"Additional selection
in the fashion sector."
Appello.
"Expected to become a bridge
between the old and new generations
through a new approach
called a traditional knot DIY kit.
Because of the expandability
and creativity of this product
two enterprises were selected
especially for the fashion sector."
- Yes!
- My gosh!
- It's us!
- Hey!
- I can't believe it!
Now, settle down.
Don't make such a fuss.
Have we decided on the person
who'll take charge
of the pop-up event with Master Im?
Not yet, sir.
Then why don't we have
Ms. Nam as the key person?
What?
Me?
Can I really do that?
She played the biggest role
in getting Master Im on board.
You know better than anyone
Master Im's conditions
and the hurdles we must clear, right?
Yes.
Yes, I'll do my best.
Hey, Da-reum!
Nice job.
- Hey, Nam Da-reum!
- I'll do my best.
My gosh. This is so great.
- My gosh.
- You have to help me.
- Of course.
- You have to.
Yes, I'll help.
TRADITION MEETS MODERN:
CUSTOMER EXPERIENCE
A REINTERPRETATION
OF KNOT-MAKING AS A BRIDGE
This area looks crowded
so let's spread it out a little.
Also, let's add a photo spot.
People can take pictures there.
Yes, a photo spot.
- Thank you, Ms. Kim.
- Sure.
Now, this area...
Or that dragonfly...
- Over here?
- There.
MAIN EXHIBITION, KNOTS ON DISPLAY?
HANBOK!
UNFRAMED: KNOTTING
UNTYING TRADITIONS TO TIE IT ANEW
It's ready.
She's working hard.
This is the main exhibition.
Master Im will demonstrate
cord-braiding here
then Director Lee will take that
and create the knots here.
That's the route.
I like that flow.
So we get to add
our modern interpretation
to the tradition Master Im made.
Yes, and we plan to add
a zone for the visitors
to experience the DIY kit
within this route.
That sounds fun.
If we hung the silk threads
here in the showroom
just like Master Im had at her place
it would add to the experience.
Yes, I'll incorporate that.
All right, then.
Okay.
Now.
All I have to do
is make good knots, then.
- Up.
- Yes.
- And here?
- Yes, and put this through.
You have to pull on this.
This way.
Like this?
Right. Let me teach you
how to do the final knot.
Sure.
From the back to the front.
- Right here?
- From the back to the front.
Wait, one more time.
From the back to the front.
And hold it with your left hand.
Anyway.
Are you turning me down?
Director Lee,
what if someone hears you?
I mean, I thought
I gave you enough time to think.
Well...
I'll try it out.
Really? Are you serious?
You can't take it back.
I won't.
You were here.
I'm sitting in a crash course
for traditional knots by Da-reum.
You should've asked me.
I'm better at that.
Aren't you busy, Mr. Kang?
I can spare that much time.
Director Lee.
Come on. What is this?
It's a mess.
You have to learn it
all over again from me.
Now, look.
Ms. Da-reum,
you can go and do your work.
Yes, right. Okay.
Please excuse me.
Ms. Da-reum, let's continue later.
She's busy.
She has to be at a meeting.
- Please excuse me.
- Sure.
First, make a V-shape.
And make two loops.
Hey, follow my steps.
- What?
- From the top.
First, make a V gesture.
Give me a V.
I want a refund.
Ma'am, there are differences
in the effect of exercise...
I don't care about that.
Your ad said
you'd help me lose weight.
So I've been coming for three months
and haven't dropped one kilogram.
Don't you owe me a refund
and compensation too?
I'm sorry, ma'am.
You've already finished the lessons
you signed up for.
So you won't give me a refund?
I'll expose you on social media.
- Ma'am.
- Contracts for sports centers
do not guarantee
on the effects when you sign up.
It's impossible to get a refund
or compensation for weight changes.
Also, you'll see in the terms
that this center does not guarantee
any change in your weight.
By any chance
have you been keeping up
with a strict diet at home?
Forget it!
- Thank you so much, sir.
- No, don't mention it.
By any chance, if you have time
I can give you tips
on dealing with different cases.
After you're done today...
Hello. Please walk in
and start warming up.
I'm sorry.
I have to start my class.
- As you should.
- Yes. Excuse me.
Mr. Min-woo.
- Yes?
- Will you come
to the last lesson of the day
next time?
- What?
- The last lesson of the day.
Yes, of course. I'll do that.
Okay. Then I'll see you next time.
I knew it.
Has she fallen
for my intellectual charms?
Well, I guess...
he's kind of cute.
You have gone off route.
Recalculating route.
Kang Ha-gi.
Are you crazy?
What are you doing here?
No.
Well, maybe just this once.
If it's not bad,
it'll be my route from now on.
Ms. Nam?
Mr. Kang!
What brings you here?
I always jog in the morning.
You can put your hands down.
I've seen it all before.
Right.
Anyway, what were you doing here?
Well, that's...
I think someone abandoned them.
It's still cold outside.
They're kittens.
I can't just leave them here.
Poor kittens.
Maybe I'll foster them for now.
Let's take them to the vet first.
They look about ten weeks old.
One is a bit smaller,
but they're both healthy.
That's good.
By any chance
I shouldn't leave them
by themselves tonight, right?
They're too young.
It's best to feed them
every three to four hours.
Do you have an important appointment?
Yes.
It's kind of hard to reschedule it
after today.
Then I'll keep them for now.
Really?
Then I'll go straight to your house
as soon as I'm done.
What?
- To my house?
- Yes.
Would that
make you feel uncomfortable?
Oh, no.
You've been to my house before.
Well, sure. Let's do that.
Thank you so much, Mr. Kang.
- If you need anything, just call me.
- Okay.
- Anyway...
- Yes?
Nothing.
You're so lucky.
Mr. Kang will watch you today.
Someone she can only meet today?
Who could that be?
The movie will start soon.
You're currently in Screen Three
on the fifth floor at Cinema Moment.
The exits are located on each side
of the theater and at the back.
In case of emergency
please follow staff instructions
and exit promptly.
For everyone's comfort and enjoyment
please switch your mobile phone
to silent or vibrate mode.
Is he not able to come?
Can I sit here?
Chan.
Do you enjoy watching horror movies?
No. Honestly, I'm kind of scared.
What about you?
Well...
I focus on their acting,
so I don't really get scared.
- Did you buy this?
- I bought it.
- Chan.
- Is it gone now?
Yes.
Did that scare you?
I was only immersed as an actor.
- Oh, you were immersed.
- I was immersed.
I got a muscle cramp.
Maybe you were too immersed.
Oh, Chan.
What about the knot?
Have you had a chance to practice?
Of course.
I practiced it like five times today
every time I had a chance.
What? Really?
What? Are you worried
that I might ruin your first project?
Yes. I'd better check.
When?
No, I was just joking.
It's a cat.
He must be cold.
I know.
He's cute. He's still a baby.
They're kittens.
I can't just leave them here.
Then I'll keep them for now.
- What's wrong?
- What?
He reminds me of a cat I know.
Hi.
Do you want to grab something hot
over there?
Oh, yes.
They requested a change
to the contract terms
but it's difficult for us
to accept it.
I'll persuade them myself in person.
Please check
the investor's schedule again.
Okay, Mr. Kang.
This is obstruction of business.
Is it warm here?
About your owner
who did she go meet?
She's taking so long.
- Soybean milk?
- Sounds good.
It's warm.
Excuse me. Aren't you Lee Chan?
- I...
- Right?
I'm a big fan of yours.
It's really him. Awesome.
And she's...
I'm...
Excuse me.
I'm just a passerby.
- You're so hot.
- You're so handsome.
- Can I have a picture?
- How are you so hot?
- You're crazy good-looking.
- My heart is going to explode.
You're unbelievably hot.
Oh, my heart is going to explode.
Let me join.
This is crazy.
His life must be tough.
Gosh, it's cold.
It is him. He's still there.
Awesome.
What a treat to see
Chan in his plain clothes.
But is he alone?
I heard he was seen with someone
in the theater.
- With whom?
- A woman.
If I get in the picture with him
that'll get him in trouble.
Chan, can I have a selfie with you?
- It's really him.
- He's so hot. I can't believe it.
Don't go.
- You're so hot.
- Excuse me. Sorry.
Where are you going?
He must be somewhere nearby.
But he seemed different today.
Didn't he look like he had company?
- Right?
- See this? It's that place.
Oh, how did I miss him?
Right. Look at that.
I barely lost them.
Where did Da-reum go?
DA-REUM
Chan, I think we should
split up for today.
Still, I had a good time.
I have work to do.
I'll head home first.
I feel bad
to send you home like this.
"I'm really fine."
Why do I keep saying I'm okay?
I'm clearly not okay.
CEO KANG HA-GI OF APPELLO
Hello?
Well...
Ms. Da-reum.
Are you
still busy?
What? Is something wrong?
That is...
The cats.
One of them sleeps too much.
I don't know much about cats.
I thought you should look into them.
Really?
I'll be there soon.
Okay.
They were sleeping until now.
It's not a lie.
I'm sorry. I hope I'm not too late.
Oh, no.
Why do you look so cold?
It's pretty cold.
I hope I didn't disturb you
when you were having fun.
Oh, not at all.
Where are the cats?
Upstairs. Come with me.
So cute.
Drink this and warm up before you go.
Oh, thank you.
- Are you okay?
- Yes, thank you.
Did they just sleep the whole time?
After I hung up the phone
they ate and played just fine.
That's good.
Thank you
for watching the kittens today.
Don't mention it.
They really hit it off
and seemed to have fun.
They hit it off?
Then I should name one Kung
and the other one Jjak, right?
The big one will be Jjak.
The small one will be Kung.
Kung and Jjak.
That works.
But I think you should separate them
for a while.
- Why is that?
- Kung keeps eating Jjak's food.
When you leave home for work,
Jjak will end up starving.
I'll watch Kung for a while.
Really?
Thank you so much, Mr. Kang.
And I've grown
attached to them already.
Do you watch Bitter Sweet too?
Because Director Lee is
starring in it.
I watch them at once to see
if anything might raise an issue.
I feel like
this is a one-sided crush.
That's not true.
I like you too.
I'm just not good
at expressing myself.
You have to say it.
I love you.
What was that?
I love you, too.
I'm jealous.
Of what?
She can be pouty and sullen
in front of the person she likes.
You are
jealous of that?
That shows how close they are.
When I like someone
I tend to keep it to myself.
But sometimes
I wish I could show how I feel.
Wanting that much
sounds like
a very healthy relationship.
Right?
I'm sorry, Ms. Da-reum.
I can't accept your heart.
If only
I hadn't been a CEO.
No, Kang Ha-gi.
Don't be swayed.
Here.
The house must feel strange
to you, Jjak.
This is where
you're going to stay for a while.
I pretended to be fine
but I was
actually very nervous today.
I'm comfortable around Mr. Kang
but why can't I do the same
with Chan?
Right?
Answer me, Jjak.
Sounds good.
Then let's have dinner on Saturday.
Okay.
You look happy these days.
Is it going well
with Da-reum or something?
Cho-yi.
Stop minding my private life
and focus on your acting.
Chan.
Don't you know that any scandal
you get caught in affects me too?
Stay low
until the show's over, will you?
Just kidding.
You wouldn't date your fan.
- We're ready for the next scene.
- Okay.
Let's go. We've got to love
each other beautifully again today.
The woman of the day.
This is for Ms. Nam Da-reum
who's in charge of the knot event.
Get everything you want.
Oh, I'm not in charge.
I'm just the youngest member.
It's not common for the youngest
to lead a big project like this.
Everyone helped me.
- Not to mention you, too.
- You're welcome.
- Now, take a look.
- Okay.
This is...
It's not even English.
What does it say?
How come there are no pictures?
- Are you ready?
- One second.
- Do you need help?
- Oh, it's okay.
It's not okay.
Just ask him for help.
Do you like fish or steak?
I'm okay with anything.
I like meat.
Do you want me to order?
Yes, please.
We'll get the dinner course
with bass and strip steak.
Has the wine I asked for last time
been aerated?
- Yes, I'll prepare it for you.
- Thank you.
I ordered different dishes
so we can share.
Sure. I'd love to.
Hello.
I made a reservation
under Kang Ha-gi.
This way, please.
This is a very nice restaurant.
Ms. Da-reum?
You must've been flustered last time.
What?
You had to leave
when my fans suddenly rushed over.
I'm sorry.
Don't mind it.
They're all your fans just like me.
I understand.
Still...
Da-reum
you're different to me.
Like I said last time
I was able to endure
the hardest time of my life
thanks to your photo book.
Chan
are you okay now?
What do you mean?
About having
a countless number of people
who love you
look for you,
and look forward to seeing you.
Things like that.
Do you want to know the truth?
Sometimes it's tough.
And it's overwhelming.
As much as people love me
I feel like I have to do well
and prove myself.
I'm afraid one mistake would bring
everything down.
WON-BIN
Maybe something urgent came up.
No, it's fine.
COCOTALK
Chan, it's urgent. Answer your phone.
- Chan.
- Yes.
Why weren't you answering your phone?
I'm outside right now.
What's up?
Director Park Chan-dong
gave us a call.
He wants to see you
at his studio right now.
I guess he liked you at the audition.
Really?
But not now.
This is more important.
Hey. Are you nuts?
This is
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
This could get you to Cannes.
No more nonsense. Wrap it up now.
I'll go pick you up now.
Da-reum, I'm sorry...
Do you have to go?
A meeting just got scheduled
for my next project.
That's really important.
The director's only available
right now.
I'm sorry.
Oh, no. It's okay.
Like you said earlier
you have to prove yourself
as much as you're loved.
Sorry about this, Da-reum.
It's really okay.
You should get going.
- I'll call you.
- Yes.
Go on.
Well, then.
We'll proceed with the contract
under the terms you proposed, Mr. Kang.
Thank you.
I appreciate your flexibility.
How was the meeting today?
I'd say it went very well.
- Good news?
- I think so.
Your party
had arranged this in advance.
MS. NAM DA-REUM
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
What's she doing alone?
She's looking this way.
That's sad.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO NAM DA-REUM
Wait, no one showed up for real?
LEE YE-JI
Sorry.
Hey. I told you. That place is lame.
The master of playing by herself.
Nam Da-reum's
legendary solo birthday party.
Are your friends running late?
They'll be here soon.
It's okay.
Mr. Kang.
- Get up.
- Sorry?
Ms. Nam.
Have you been
going on blind dates by any chance?
Blind dates?
Last time, when you asked me
to watch the cats
and even today.
Oh, right.
Yes, it's a blind date.
If you're trying to get over
someone you like
don't bother.
You don't need
to let go of your feelings.
Okay.
Anyway, did he leave without you?
Well...
I was kind of flustered too.
But it happens.
- I'm okay.
- But you're not.
You always say
you're okay.
I guess people won't feel as bad
when you say that.
But you're hurt.
At least, in front of me
you can say it's not okay.
Okay.
To be honest
it wasn't okay.
It's okay.
When I pretend to be okay
I look
less pitiful.
"I'm really fine."
It's really okay.
You should get going.
I've always swallowed it.
But today, it kind of hurts.
Don't meet anyone like that.
Ms. Nam Da-reum.
You deserve better than that.
You don't deserve to date a jerk
who leaves you on a blind date.
That jerk is your friend.
Why are you smiling?
No, it's nothing.
Maybe something more important
than me came up.
Still, for some reason
it's less disappointing today.
Perhaps because I'm walking with you.
I think
I feel better.
The air is nice.
This is a lot better
than the blind date.
I should go home
but I don't want to.
Why not?
Because
I want to stay like this.
Sorry?
Because of Kung.
He doesn't stop running at night
as if he's possessed.
Jjak too.
Apparently, when they're kittens,
they have too much energy to handle.
If Jjak doesn't sleep during the day,
he runs so much at dawn.
So I keep waking up at dawn.
If they live together,
it'll be war every day.
But then
if they stay together,
they'll be less lonely.
This is Jjak from earlier today.
He was enjoying the sunlight,
then he dozed off.
Just like the owner.
So bright and gentle.
It's the first snow this season.
It's pretty.
Yes.
So pretty.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
Do you want to meet outside?
How can Mr. Kang be fine?
He's such a pro.
To be honest... Wait!
I liked him for a very long time.
LA?
Why don't you come with me?
Whoever he is
you don't need to put up
with him that much.
Are you protecting your employee
or are you keeping me in check?
Mr. Kang, the truth is...
- Is this...
- Chan, where are you going?
Is this true?
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs